Jhal Hello everyone welcome back to my channel
Keep creating friends in today's first video
we will
see all the important news and indicators from Liberty Market
India ratings have given
negative revision to the rates of banking and financial industry from the table,
so it is estimated that
right now there are very uncertain times for the banking sector On the
basis of all the news and indicators, which are the
fundamentals that you
should consider while investing and at which graduation
level you can do them, we will
discuss that in this video
Before starting the video let me tell you that if you have
not subscribed to the channel till now then Yo Honey
Singh and 9 News Formation of Years Before
Investing and Wealth Creation Your
subscriptions, likes and comments give me more
motivation and I
try to create videos from your members and topics, so just
like button
subscribe to the channel and do not forget to
press on the friend notification so that not a single one of the upcoming videos comes  Do
n't miss the video. You
can also follow us on Facebook, computer, and television
to enhance your knowledge and your savings. The link is
given in the description. So, without taking any
time, let's get started.
Friends, in today's video, we will discuss many banking
and finance services limited stocks.
All the stocks are
for BFSI sector. But there are a lot of
stocks from that chapter as well. I feel that the
fundamentals from these stocks can give you
significant wealth creation in the long term.
And at what price
level can they be applied? We are going to discuss all of these.
Before starting, let me tell you that in this video,
we will not discuss many different aspects of Escorts. So,
if
I cover the fundamentals of all these stocks in one video, the
video will become very long. So, this
video is not for that purpose. In this video,
we are going to discuss which
fundamentally strong stocks of these stocks can be
taken at a low price. But whatever
we will discuss here,
I will create short videos for them one by one.
I have already made a video on the fundamental analysis of HDFC Bank.
If you haven't seen that video yet, you
can check it out.
I'll put the link in the upper right corner. You
can understand the
fundamental difference by watching that video. HDFC Bank is
my favorite bank in India. I
think HDFC Bank is the best bank in India.
Why is that so? In that video, we have added many
designs, many ratios, many
numbers, and we have tried to understand
why HDFC Bank is on the
top fundamentally. So, you
can take a quick overview in that video. HDFC Bank is
one of the favorites, but anyway,
as I said, I will keep creating separate videos of all these stars
for the
details of fundamental analysis.
In this video, we will try to write the price labels of all those stars. So,
our first part today is about HDFC Bank,
India's number one private bank. The
governor of India, best friend Anupama
McKay. India's best friend, Tasty C.  The
market capitalization of the bank is
around Rs 6 lakh crore. It is a very big bank. The
bank with the largest market capitalization in India,
124. Currently, many of the banking and finance
sector's staff are
not reporting to duty because the RBI
suggested them to
preserve their queries
because the situation going forward is very
uncertain. Therefore, they do not want
banks to delete their cash on dividends.
Therefore, you might be
seeing a little less dividend currently, but
in the future, when the situation normalizes, this
dividend will also go up.
Its dividend is 1.09, so it is a
little higher than the market.
For those who are watching our market analysis videos for the first time, let us
tell you that if the dividend is more than 54, then
we believe that the stock market is
higher than the dividend, and if the dividend is less than the dividend, then
we believe that the
particular staff you are using is lower than the
overall market.  And Nifty or 19518
to monitor, its beta is
slightly higher than 1.0 or 1.1, so it is
slightly higher than the market. We also
discussed this in previous videos that sectors, especially for example, the
banking and finance sector, have
times when the overall market conditions are slightly higher. Similarly, such sectors,
especially for example, China, are much lower than the market. So,
for general information, you can understand that
beta is an indicator of quality.
At 2030, you are
getting it cheaper than the industries price. So,
you are getting such a good bank at a
lower valuation than the industries price. And people are
also buying its delivery at a good level. The
percentage is 30%, respectively.
If you look at this chart, if
you find this stock in the middle of the range, then this can be a
very good level for long term investment.
But we
want all of you investors to be a little weighty
when we saw that there is a
lot of uncertainty and instability in the banking and finance sector industry right now.  It is
possible
that if some politics is done in the short term
and this interest comes down a little, then
if it is more than 250 then what to say,
it is a very good option for the long term,
but if you find it anywhere in this range
then you can cancel the investment in this bank
because it is such a
strong bank, its fundamentals are so good
that it will definitely give you a good classification in the long term, this is
my
opinion.
Our other staff members have talked
about ICICI Lombard a couple of times,
but I want you
not to miss this post, so I have again
reviewed
ICICI Lombard, one of the leading market players in the private sector in the general insurance sector,
its market capitalization is almost
around 1500, slightly less among the students, the
finance sector is a
little less, point to 7, 10 point note, it is almost the same as the
market, it
is a little less than the market because
generally you will see that the
apps related to the insurance sector are
not as volatile as the ones  Fan Club and the other
thing is that even though they are financial sector
stocks, they do have some quality,
but still compared to
banks and embassies, rib complaints to small
penis and small embassies, they are monitored much less
because their business,
life insurance, general insurance,
all of these businesses are quite
stable. Well, friends, they are quite
stable, so they are being valued by
very
policymakers. You can see here
this point industry training and you are
getting a slight premium valuation of almost 6%. Even on this, people are
taking a very good delivery of 4%. So this
shows you how much confidence they have
in the stop and people are taking a good amount of delivery.
Setting its price,
if you see it at the level of 1250 to 13, then
this can be a very handsome level
for long term investment. But if you
want to wait a little and in the short term, if it
falls a little, then
if you see it between 11 and 1150, then go
long.  It could be a very
good level for the long term. At that time, you
can definitely invest in it. Our
third stock is also in the banking and financial
services industry. HDFC AMC,
which also plays in the Asif Management Company service,
I consider HDFC AMC to be the best player in that list.
Its fundamentals, its
systems and processes, and its
operations, I think HDFC
AMC is quite good.
You are seeing a significant decline in it in recent times, and
you might be wondering what the future holds for the mutual fund
industry. Everyone is
investing as directors now,
everyone is taking directors, so
I am seeing opposition and staff and their features,
but Muzaffar, there is a lot of future for the industry.
You may feel like this right now, but
in the long term, I think that when normalcy returns, people will
again go back to the mutual fund
front because the
benefits of mutual funds are still in place. There is
no fundamental change in it.
Due to short-term sentiment, of long-term
investments in focus, remove your name from
my post.  So if you want to invest in asset management
companies and asset management in the general sector, then
HDFC AMC is one of the best backers
for you. It has a strong market
capitalization.
Despite being a stock with a factor of 1.26, the
demand for this company is quite handsome. From there, the
upward difference, which should be
1.26, is that
its price is less than the market price. Its price is
around 30 p.m. of the industry or
you are getting a slight
prevention from 37-7. This stop had gone to a very
good level. Almost, I was getting it
at the price level of 37-38.
Now, as you can see here, you are
getting it only, so it is available to
you at a very good valuation.
And
also look at the price chart to see at which level you
can take a position in it. You can see that at
this price level, it has a
good delivery percentage on this stock. In what
good amount people have put it
in their investment account.  We're taking it for
such a great day. It shows you
how much confidence there is in it, and people are
taking delivery of it by loading it into their long-term investing accounts. So, there's a
very strong delivery-per-centage-per-centage-
delivery deficiency of 75%. If you look at its chart, the
current whiskey market
price is there. You can also click on it in MS Word.
You can see that the
error for the last March close of around 120 is
only 10% above its
five-year high. So, you're still
getting it at a very good valuation. In my view,
if you want to invest in it for the long term,
you
can also take interest in it at current market levels. If you
want to wait a little longer and see
how the stock performs, you
can also use the near future forecast of 2018. If it
reaches that level, it will be
around 120 for its market cap. If it is at that level,
you can definitely comment on investing in it.
And long then, our next banking
stocks are Kotak Mahindra Bank and HDFC Bank.
Additionally, if I like another bank at the market
level, it's Kotak Mahindra Bank. Its
market capitalization is around 2.5 lakh crore rupees, so it's a
fairly large bank. It's also a
Dr. Samay mentioned that the RBI has
told banks not to devalue. This is its
current rate, but going forward, it could also be a
good rate of devaluation.
As we discussed, banking stocks
generally trade slightly higher than the market.
Its rate is 1.12,
slightly higher than the industry's rate of 126.
You're getting 43,000 at a slightly premium valuation.
This stock is slightly overvalued compared to HDFC Bank. We'll discuss at
what price level it should be bought. Its
delivery percentage is around a small percentage,
which is respectable. It's not too high,
but not too low. So,
if you look at the price chart of Kotak Mahindra Bank, its
current market price is
between 55013 and 55013. Which I think could be
a good entry point
if you invest in it.  If you want to wait a little
and you get all this between 1100 and 1150, then
that can be a
very strong level for investment, so anywhere in between, so
you can
cancel the investment. Planning and comfort
level and water pollution. If you have a
good position and you
want to make a good portion in this pack, then
you can invest anywhere in the middle of this range.
But Ko Tiffin Pack is fundamentally a
very strong stock. You should
definitely keep it in your voter list.
Next, Stockholm CG Kawardha Market
Leaders Breed-by-Breed is a multinational NCC
company. Its market capitalization is
around 1.5 lakh crore. Depends on this very
impressive. Tasty
points to around 2.1C. So, as we talked about, important
seat stocks are much lower than the general market. So,
we can see that the
points to Ko's son shows that breeds are
much lower than the overall market. As a
generation of the search industry, this gives you  If it is available in the middle of the back of 7475, then it
is available at a little premium. Very high
values ​​for the current market price. I do
not think so. You can see its delivery percentage. They will
give a very handsome delivery percentage of five percent. As we have seen
in the earlier videos also, we
talked about that matter. You can keep an eye on it at the
price level of 15,000 to 16,000.
This investment can be good
for long term investment, but
if you want to wait a little, although
I do not expect it to fall so soon in the near term,
but if it
comes in the market and if you
get it between 13,000 to 14,000, then you
can definitely invest in the office.
Attack price level.
Hello friends, another giant of this sector,
Hindustan Unilever, is our next
topic. Its market application is
around 5 lakh crores and its
matriculation is much bigger than Pune. Its deal is also
quite handsome, around 1.64, son.  It is
set from a point, so as we have seen that we are
less volatile than the stock market, this is
also a complete file of the industry, it is
around the Senate, you are getting it around the back of the industry,
one to keep and its
David percentage is also very handsome, sixty
five percent, a strong 10:00 percent
and you are getting it at a good price,
people are taking delivery of it at a good level,
Joshi's current market price is
around 21, so
how can you definitely invest in it at this level,
you can see that this cream had reached the level of 26,
then it declined
and now it is running at almost a level of one rupee,
so if you get it for one rupee and 150, then
you
can make necessary investment in it for the long term,
but if you want to wait a little, then if the
level of 2000 to 2050 comes in it, you
can definitely check the investment in the office on that price channel, ITC,
as we have discussed in the previous one or two videos.
It was discussed in great detail that although it is
considered a CG player, but
still a major percentage of its revenue and profit goes to
cigarettes, hence it is
considered an 11th and bean playing player,
now we are in the vegetable sector, that is why I have
inputted it here,
you are getting a good price for travel, its market
capitalization is around 220000 crores,
dividend is very good, compatible with FD,
5.7% return is very good, you will have it,
you have a
price which is much lower than the market,
around 1515 of the industry, you are
getting it at the price of the industry,
on holiday, it is not at all overvalued,
I do not find the stock serious at the price level,
delivery percentage is a loss of 50%, sub
delivery percentage is,
as we talked about, it can be
taken between the current market price, if you get
anywhere between 118 to 128, then you
can cancel the investment in it for the long term, the plate is in the top  You will have to be
very patient, throw it in the bud,
its price movement has not been good for the last three-four years,
apart from this, it will give you a very good
debit, so this company provides
you double dividend for the interest you get in your bank savings account,
although it has the most significant capital
appreciation, so if you can have a little patience in this, then
I
see good future growth in the country's G sector and
when its liberating feature is low, then
you will see good capital appreciation in it,
after the daughter, 12791 level can be a
good level for investment,
if you want to wait a little and you feel it is
between 160 to 170, then you
can definitely consider ITC for investment,
our next element is HDFC Limited,
we talked about HDFC Bank,
talked about HDFC AMC, in the first few videos we
also saw HDFC Life and our
parent company is HDFC Limited, a
limited holding company on behalf of all these many
powerful businesses, so it is one
of the best in India.  BSE
Business: HDFC Ltd. can be a
very good long-term investment.
Its market capitalization is around 3 lakh
crores (Daniel is quite handsome at 1.2 per cent and
St. Son School at 1.24 per cent). So, pension sector
stocks are a little higher. Compared to the market, the BTech is a little
more volatile. The
drafting of the industry and this gives you a
stronger team. The payment is not too much. There is no overt
Bollywood talk at all. The
current market price of the delivery percentage can give you an idea of
whose delivery people are taking by filling their investment accounts. A
very respectable delivery percentage of almost 3 percent.
If we talk about its price chart, you can see
that its current market price is in the same
range. If
you get it from the enemies, between 1750 and 14, 2008, then you can
definitely cancel your long-term investment in it.
HDFC Ltd. is one of the best complement businesses in India and
in the long term, it can send you a good amount of money.
It has created considerable wealth for many people.  It has created a
legacy and
changed their lives, and for the future, I like its
prospects for growth. If you
can hold HDFC Ltd for rates
on rent, if you want to wait a little longer,
you
can wait for the 1516 level to do this. If that
trend hits you, it could be a great
level. For long-term interest,
HDFC Ltd has
our final stop, and that too is
another factor. Bajaj Finserv.
You must have heard about Bajaj Finance.
Understand that Bajaj Finserv is a paint
company. Bajaj Finance also comes under Bajaj Finserv.
Bajaj's general
insurance and life insurance business
also come under it. So, if you invest in Bajaj Finserv, then
you should not only use an
MBBS seat holder, Bajaj Finance's arm is
BSc in general, but also
its life insurance and general insurance
business. Hearing the name of Bajaj Allianz,
Bajaj Allianz is also a business of Bajaj Finserv. So,
when you invest in Bajaj Finserv,
You invest in these three systems -
BSNL Life Insurance and Channel
Missions. Always keep this in mind. The
market place dividend of Bajaj Finserv
is very low around the year 20.08 like in
America. Most of the pension sector
companies are never giving good dividends,
so now its dividend is
looking very low. Its RD is 1.34,
which shows that it is much higher than the market. If you are from the
finance sector, then the
real quality will be in it. If you are interested in this, then
around the holidays you will have to
pay 140 rupees at a very high premium valuation. But the reason for this premium valuation is
that its price will be a little less,
due to which yellow mustard has become quite inflated
and this stock used to
trend at around 10,000 level.
If you would have seen in February four-five months ago,
it used to trend at around 10,000 level
and you are getting it at the price level of 6000 now. So
you are getting a discount of 14% on the collection of 44%.
The percentage isn't anything special. The borderline is okay,
so it shows that you
can also put some weight in it. So, if you
develop some quality, you
can activate it on that platform. If you
look at its price set, you can see
that its market price is
hovering around this range.
If you find this top between childhood and questions, then
you
can definitely invest in it. For example, if we talked about it,
you see, this stock was
trading at the level of 10,000 during the time of family, so
from that level, you are currently
getting it at a discount of more than 40%,
so this can be a very attractive level.
But if you should wait a little more,
if you want to print your long-term investment,
first in the spot and then
want to invest. If you want to be a little smarter, then
you
can also put weight on the level from 4000 to 45. If it reaches that level,
it can be a very promising and excellent level.
Bajaj Finserv is an excellent option for long-term investment.  It is a very
fundamentalist and company, its business is a
very good system, Bajaj Finance has a
paint instead, then you can understand
how great its prospective and
future is,
friends, this was today's video, in
which the knowledge power can be achieved, the master of this channel is to
bring the right knowledge to you
and in every upcoming video we will
discuss many interesting offices
and I am bringing you the user  I will tell you about ID or injury in the office.
Similarly, every weekend we will discuss weekly
market updates and our views on situations like Dr. Karna. So
definitely subscribe to the channel and if
you liked the next video update then like the video. If
you think that this information
can help someone then share it with your friends and
family members and
subscribe to the channel. In our next video
with the description of the job, till then
come to Tech's NCC on uska.